(Leonard:)-Hey.
-Laser.
(Howard:)Had a great night last night.
(Howard:)I don't like to kiss and tell,
but somebody made it to eighth base.
(Leonard:)-What the hell is eighth base?
-Seventh base with shirt off.
(Howard:)Well, my shirt.
(Howard:)-How'd things go with Penny?
-Oh, couldn't be better.
(Howard:)Are we taking
our relationship frustrations out...
(Howard:)...on innocent Cylons?
(Leonard:)It's not just Cylons. Superman's next.
I was gonna try to squeeze in
a little more mocking before lunch...
...but I can come back when
you don't have a high-powered weapon.
(Leonard:)How can I go out with a woman
who believes in psychics?
(Howard:)Hey, I once dated a girl who believed
she was abducted by aliens.
(Leonard:)And that didn't bother you?
(Howard:)Au contraire, it meant she was gullible
and open to a little probing.